<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[make a difference]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[make a difference]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/make-a-difference/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2016 02:12:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/make-a-difference/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[10 Tips for selling local food to restaurants]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>10 Tips for selling local food to restaurants</h1><p>Do not call restaurants at random. - Find specific restaurants that might need your product and target those.If you already sell to other restaurants, let the chef know. - Name names. Knowing that you sell to other restaurants makes us more comfortable in dealing with you.Find out the chef’s and owner’s names - The chef is the person who usually makes the decisions on what to buy. These people are frequently the same person in small restaurants.Visit or call on a slow day (Tuesday or Wednesday – in the mid afternoon.) - Do not call over lunch, dinner or on Fridays or Saturdays.Take a sample - You need to get your product in the mouth of the chef. Go to the restaurant with a sample of your product, a small sample, preferably ready to eat.Sell Flavour - chefs want flavour. They know it is hard to make great tasting food without amazing ingredientsIf your product requires cooking, take you product cooked – do not season or flavour it, but a little salt is OK. Remember, you are not selling a dish, you are selling an ingredient, and the chef need to taste what you are selling, not taste what s/he can do with it.Try and understand your market and their needs. Small high-end restaurants need small amounts of specialty products. High volume casual are going to need large amounts of cost effective product.Most chefs do not want the bulk of their products on Saturday. We need the products in the restaurant Wednesday or Thursday so we can prep them for our busiest days.If all else fails, make a reservation and take a sample of you product. Go in for dinner (on a slow day) and ask to speak to the owner. They will take the sample from you, you are their customer.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/9fbff060acc48bd4954252e6c35e05b8ef478310.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://mashable.com/2016/04/02/tricks-to-make-your-food-taste-better/#VjpZmG0f9iqK</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4c0bad65-cc5d-409d-84c9-e9cddf04b70c</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2016 17:53:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[10 Benefits of a Local Food System]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>10 Benefits of a Local Food System</h1><p>Why Eat Local?</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/0ab454f413305f97bc73c1b1bc5d79161bd9cef2.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.wallpaper.com/lifestyle/theres-brew-love-in-a-new-lager-saga-daniel-noah-sheikh-reinvents-beer</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9f98ba3a-3449-4394-b153-6efeae897321</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 12:16:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TEDxEdmonton - Jessie Radies - How Local Transforms Communities]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>TEDxEdmonton - Jessie Radies - How Local Transforms Communities</h1><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/df22c9fa19015b44628ce9785b7b0f42e7f5dba4.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oV7ImWO55K4</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d1c1e646-cadd-4a5c-8f67-99f6b46fa37e</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 03:46:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>